

# **OMAR BRADAI**

Al Engineer

omarbradai142@gmail.com

+216 20 681 965

Tunisia, Ben arous, El mourouj 3

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

As a dedicated and motivated individual, I am deeply passionate about the field of Artificial Intelligence. With a strong academic foundation and a thirst for more experience, I am committed to contributing to the advancement of the industry and its transformative potential.

# **EDUCATION**

# **National Institute of Applied Science and Technology**

09/2019 - 09/2024

- · University of Carthage, Tunisia
- Degree: Industrial Computing and Automation Engineering, specialized in Data science.

10/2013 - 10/2018

#### British council, Tunis, Tunisia

• Degree: First Certificate in English (FCE) with a C1 level in English

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### EmyeHR, Data science engineering intern

04/2024 - 08/2024

- Optimized integration between chat agents and the Emye bot, focusing on prompt quality and cost efficiency.
- Fine-tuned GPT-3.5 for precise and efficient SQL generation tailored to company data.
- Developed an automatic synthetic data generating program using GPT.
- Developed benchmarking systems to evaluate agent performance and visualize results effectively.
- Conducted **R&D** on **Al-driven** systems for predicting employee behavioral trends and resignation, utilizing **online** and **batch machine learning**, customized for EmyeHR clients' personal data.

# Influence Consulting, Machine learning intern

07/2023 - 09/2023

- Developed an automatic speech recognition ai model fine tuned on the Tunisian dialect.
- Created a dataset for the ASR model with 1000+ transcriptions and +1h of recordings using multiple data sources.
- cleaning and processing techniques using NumPy, OpenCV and TensorFlow
- Developed the infrastructure of the web platform for the project using terraform, AWS, docker as well as other tools for DevOps such as bitbucket.

# Tnker, Mobile development intern

06/2023 - 08/2023

- Developed a flutter mobile app prototype for voice calling that handles 4 servers simultaneously.
- Integrated the voice calling prototype as a feature in the final product app.

## Additional work experience

2021-2022

- Automation engineering intern at NATILAIT (Dairy company)
- · Network engineering intern at Discovery Informatique

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILL**

- Python / C++ / JavaScript / Flutter
- TensorFlow / NumPy / OpenCV / LLM / ML
- GIT / Azure / AWS / Postgres / Bitbucket

- LANGUAGESEnglish (C1)
- Arabic (Native)
- French (Intermidate)